<resources>
    <string name="app_name">sentio</string>
    <string name="title_section1">Home</string>
    <string name="title_section2">Calendar</string>
    <string name="title_section3">Clubs</string>
    <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_club_page">ClubPageActivity</string>
    <string name="name"><b>Name:</b></string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string-array name="description_array">
        <item>EnviroStories is an organization of students teaching fellow students how they can reduce their carbon footprint and the beneficial impact that reduction will create. In our annual summer camp, Camp Footprint, we explore with elementary-aged kids the aspects of an ecosystem, how humans affect the environment, and behavioral and technological methods for reducing that impact. Throughout the school year we work to make STEM a greener school by encouraging students to reduce their waste and teachers to use lights less.</item>
        <item>Ethics Bowl is a national competition for high school students in which teams prepare responses to a set of cases on topics ranging from the use of immunization programs as a cover for spying operations to preventing uninsured motorists from refueling to the utterly entertaining (*cough* “please discuss the ethical dimensions of dating your friend’s ex” *cough*). On competition day, we present our cases and discuss them with schools from around Seattle, and through the process, have the opportunity to extend any given topic much further than we ever thought possible.</item>
        <item>FBLA is a club that allows students to gain and sharpen their business skills in a real-world environment. Through competitions at the regional, state, and national level, students get to flex their skills in presentation, public speaking, and knowledge across a variety of fields, ranging from computer skills to business ethics and law.</item>
        <item>HOSA is a national organization of future health professionals that promotes careers in health and medicine through a number of competitive events ranging from knowledge tests to presentations and projects. The goal of HOSA is to stimulate conversation about the ever-changing and expanding field of medicine and how we can shape it in the years to come.</item>
        <item>We are a club oriented around alleviating community suffering and integrating students with the medical community. In partnership with the American Red Cross, we aim to equip our members with the right mind and skill set to make measurable impacts as medical volunteers and leaders to our peers through fundraising, volunteering with health professionals, and basic essential medical training. As part of our joint mission with the American Red Cross, we mobilize the power of volunteers and the generosity of donors to prevent and alleviate human suffering in the face of emergencies.</item>
        <item>At math club, we don’t just sit around and discuss calculus all week. That’s only what we do every other week! In reality, we spend a lot of time participating in competitions and representing Tesla STEM. We do online competitions with other schools around the nation, as well as local competitions facing rivals Interlake and Redmond.</item>
        <item>In an era of globalization, foreign policy and international relations are increasingly becoming a large facet of progress and prosperity. In Model United Nations, students address global problems and work to create solutions in real world context. By acting as delegates from a representative country in the United Nations, students learn about diplomacy, international relations, and national policy from the perspective of their respective country -- making the simulation of a United Nations Conference as real as ever.</item>
        <item>This club is such an important outlet and inspiration for creativity. I love STEM subjects, but I love art too, and this is the closest thing to an art class that I can take since I completed graphic design in 9th grade. It also has really helped me to grow as a leader and a planner.</item>
        <item>National Honor Society is a great way to become part of the community and
            volunteer locally throughout the year!</item>
        <item>Peer Tutor Lab gives students the opportunity to get academic help from their peers on any number of school subjects.</item>
        <item>PHASER physics club welcomes physics enthusiasts to join us as we build telescopes, study for the Physics Olympiad test, and generally explore the universe around us! All are welcome regardless of previous knowledge.</item>
        <item>Quantum Robotics club satisfies the hunger we have for engineering and technology
            by offering the opportunity to participate in VEX robotics. Club members form teams
            to design, build, and compete with robots through many tournaments throughout the
            year. By championing and collecting awards through these tournaments, teams must
            climb the ladder of competitions from regionals to state to the ultimate goal of any
            VEX robotics team: the VEX Worlds Championships. Last year 3 Quantum teams qualified
            for Vex Worlds.</item>
        <item>Cancer has affected all of us in one way or another. Relay for Life, the primary fundraiser for the American Cancer Society, is one way everyone, even if they don’t have cancer, can fight back against a disease which takes too many lives. That is why, as a club we serve the mission: “The hope that those lost to cancer will never be forgotten, that those who face cancer will be supported, and that one day cancer will be eliminated.</item>
        <item>Science Bowl is a fast-paced, beyond intense competition where teams of 5 prepare hard for the Department of Energy funded event. Besides the intense studying, the team dynamic must be impeccable, buzzing skills to be fine-tuned, and focus to be sharp. From the thrill of instinctive buzzing in to the mind-boggling questions, Science Bowl is a fun and dynamic learning environment.</item>
        <item>TSA, or the Terminal Security Administra. . . No. Although we are commonly mistaken
            for the mighty task force charged with the mission of ensuring the safety of the
            lives of air-bound civilians, STEM\'s very own TSA was formed for an even more noble cause. The STEM TSA Chapter aims to provide the opportunity for students to engage in many different areas of technology ranging from robotics to video production in order to extend the STEM experience from classrooms to real world scenarios.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cname_array">
        <item>Caeli MacLennan</item>
        <item>Sonia Murthy</item>
        <item>Maya Ganesan</item>
        <item>Sonia Murthy</item>
        <item>Teri Guo</item>
        <item>Udit Ranasaria</item>
        <item>Nivi Thomas</item>
        <item>Amy Zhang</item>
        <item>Christina Dias</item>
        <item>Tiago Ferreira</item>
        <item>Ben Zabback</item>
        <item>Mrigank Bhardwaj</item>
        <item>Juliana Seymour</item>
        <item>Udit Ranasaria</item>
        <item>Alka Pai</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cmail_array">
        <item>s-cmaclennan@lwsd.org</item>
        <item>s-smurthy@lwsd.org</item>
        <item>mayaganesan@gmail.com</item>
        <item>s-somurthy@lwsd.org</item>
        <item>s-tguo@lwsd.org</item>
        <item>s-uranasaria@lwsd.org</item>
        <item>s-nthomas@lwsd.org</item>
        <item>s-azhang@lwsd.org</item>
        <item>s-cdias@lwsd.org</item>
        <item>s-tferriera@lwsd.org</item>
        <item>s-bzabback@lwsd.org</item>
        <item>s-mbhardwaj@lwsd.org</item>
        <item>s-jseymour@lwsd.org</item>
        <item>s-uranasaria@lwsd.org</item>
        <item>s-apai@lwsd.org</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>